let questions = [
    {
        numb:1,
        question : " Age of Umesh will be 4 times the age of Reena in 6 years from today. If ages of Umesh and Mahesh are 7 times and 6 times the age of Reena respectively, what is present age of Umesh?",
        answer : "42 years",
        options :[
            "33 years",
            "42 years",
            "48 years",
            "40 years"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question : "Rohan's age is five times Ajay’s and seven-eighteenth of Meena’s age. The sum of the ages of all three of them is 132 years. How much younger is Ajay to Meena?",
        answer : "83 years",
        options :[
            "56 years",
            "44 years",
            "87 years",
            "83 years"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question : "The average age of 10 students and their teacher is 15 years. The average age of the first seven students is 15 yr and that of the last three is 11 yr. What is the teacher's age?",
        answer : "27 years",
        options :[
            "20 years",
            "27 years",
            "87 years",
            "30 years"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question : "Ram and Shyam’s average age is 65 years. The average age of Ram, Shyam and John is 53 years. What is the age of John?",
        answer : "29 years",
        options :[
            "29 years",
            "35 years",
            "24 years",
            "39 years"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question : "The present ages of Aman and Nina are 59 and 37 years, respectively. What was the ratio of the ages of Nina and Aman 13 years ago?",
        answer : "12:23",
        options :[
            "12:33",
            "15:22",
            "12:23",
            "12:48"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question : "Average age of a family of 4 members was 19 years, 4 years back. Birth of a new child kept the average age of the family same even today. How old is the child today?",
        answer : "3 years",
        options :[
            "7 years",
            "5 years",
            "2 years",
            "3 years"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question : "12 years ago, age of P was 3 times the age of Q. After 12 years, ratio of ages of Q to P will be 2:3. What is the present age of P?",
        answer : "36 years",
        options :[
            "47 years",
            "36 years",
            "34 years",
            "55 years"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question : "The average age of a group of 4 friends is 36 years. The youngest friend amongst them is 6 years old. What was the average age of the group at the time of the birth of the youngest friend?",
        answer : "40 years",
        options :[
            "40 years",
            "43 years",
            "36 years",
            "85 years"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question : "The combined age of husband and wife on their 20th wedding anniversary was twice than it was at the time of wedding. If the husband is 3 years older than his wife. How old was he at the time of his marriage?",
        answer : "21.5 years",
        options :[
            "25.5 years",
            "21.8 years",
            "25.9 years",
            "21.5 years"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question : "The average age of 19 boys and the class teacher is 16 years. If the ages of the class teacher and one of the boys are excluded, the average age reduces to 15 years. What is the age of the class teacher ?",
        answer : "Data Inadequate",
        options :[
            "Data Inadequate",
            "26 years",
            "36 years",
            "46 years"     
       ]
    },
   
]
